(Sheldon:)Will you two please inform Amy
how much you enjoy
(Sheldon:)adhering
to a strict bathroom schedule?
(Amy:)- Can't.
- Won't.
(Leonard:)- Didn't.
- Don't.
(Amy:)I told you,
(Amy:)you can't regulate every aspect
of our lives.
(Sheldon:)I can if you'd just roll over
and accept your fate.
(Amy:)I'm sorry
for bringing this over here.
(Penny:)Believe me, we know
what you're going through.
And I-I think the most helpful
thing we can tell you is
(Leonard:)no backsies.
(Penny:)Mm-hmm.
(Amy:)Sheldon,
I understand
(Amy:)that you like things
a certain way
(Amy:)and I'm willing
to make some concessions,
(Amy:)but you have to be open
to compromise.
(Penny:)She's right.
That's reasonable.
(Sheldon:)Oh, look who's in
favor of compromise,
(Sheldon:)the woman who married
Leonard Hofstadter.
(Leonard:)Hey, she didn't
compromise.
(Leonard:)She settled.
There's a difference.
(Penny:)Yeah. You tell him, babe.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪